NVIDIA (R) Compute Sanitizer
Copyright (c) 2020-2021 NVIDIA Corporation
Version 2021.1.0
Usage: compute-sanitizer [options] [your-program] [your-program-options]

General options:
  -h [ --help ]                         Produce this help message.
  -v [ --version ]                      Print the version number.
  --binary-patching arg (=yes)          Control the binary patching of the device code.
                                        Disabling this option will result in a loss of precision for error reporting.
  --check-api-memory-access arg (=yes)  Check cudaMemcpy/cudaMemset for accesses to device memory
  --check-device-heap arg (=yes)        Check allocation on the device heap.
  --check-exit-code arg (=yes)          Check application exit code and print an error if it is different than 0
  --demangle arg (=full)                Demangle function names.
                                        full   : Show demangled function name, including parameters, templates, etc
                                        simple : Show demangled function name, without parameters, templates, etc
                                        no     : Show mangled function name
  --destroy-on-device-error arg (=context)
                                        Behavior of compute-sanitizer on a precise device error.
                                        NOTE: Imprecise errors will always destroy the context.
                                        context : CUDA context is terminated with an error.
                                        kernel  : Kernel is terminated. Subsequent kernel launches are still allowed.
  --error-exitcode arg                  When this is set, compute-sanitizer will return the given exitcode when any errors are detected.
  --exclude arg                         key1=val1,key2=val2,...
                                        The exclude option can be used to control the kernels that will not be checked by the tool
                                        Multiple exclude options can be defined. Each option is additive, so kernels matching
                                        any specified pattern will be excluded
                                        If this option is specified with filter option(s), only kernels matching at least one
                                        filter pattern and not matching any exclude patterns will be checked.
                                        Exclusions are specified as key value pairs, with each pair separated by a ','
                                        Keys have both a long form, and a shorter form for convenience.
                                        Valid values for keys are:
                                            kernel_name, kne      : The value is the full mangled name of the kernel
                                            kernel_substring, kns : The value is a substring in the mangled name of the kernel
  --filter arg                          key1=val1,key2=val2,...
                                        The filter option can be used to control the kernels that will be checked by the tool
                                        Multiple filter options can be defined. Each option is additive, so kernels matching
                                        any specified filter will be checked
                                        Filters are specified as key value pairs, with each pair separated by a ','
                                        Keys have both a long form, and a shorter form for convenience.
                                        Valid values for keys are:
                                            kernel_name, kne      : The value is the full mangled name of the kernel
                                            kernel_substring, kns : The value is a substring in the mangled name of the kernel
  --force-blocking-launches arg (=no)   Force launches to be blocking.
  --force-synchronization-limit arg (=0)
                                        Set the maximum number of launches occurring on a given stream without forcing a synchronization.
                                        A lower value can help reducing tools usage of device memory at the cost of performances.
                                        A zero value sets no limit. A one value is equivalent to --force-blocking-launches.
  --injection-path arg                  Set the path to injection libraries.
  --language arg (=c)                   <c|fortran> This option can be used to enable language specific behavior. When set to fortran, the thread and block indices
                                        of messages printed by compute-sanitizer will start with 1-based offset to match Fortran semantics.
  --launch-timeout arg (=10)            Timeout in seconds to wait to connect to the target process. A value of zero forces compute-sanitizer to wait infinitely.
  --log-file arg                        File where compute-sanitizer will write all of its text output. If not specified, compute-sanitizer output is written to stdout.
                                        The sequence %p in the string name will be replaced by the pid of the compute-sanitizer application.
                                        The sequence %q{FOO} will be replaced by the value of the environment variable FOO. If the environment variable
                                        is not defined, it will be replaced by an empty string
                                        The sequence %% is replaced with a literal % in the file name.
                                        Any other character following % will cause an error.
  --max-connections arg (=10)           Maximum number of ports for connecting to target application
  --kill arg (=yes)                     Makes the compute-sanitizer kill the target application when having a communication error.
  --mode arg (=launch-and-attach)       Select the mode of interaction with the target application:
                                          launch-and-attach
                                          (launch and attach for profiling)
                                          launch
                                          (launch and suspend for later attach)
                                          attach
                                          (attach to launched application)
  --nvtx arg (=no)                      Enable NVTX support.
  --port arg (=49152)                   Base port for connecting to target application
  --prefix arg (==========)             Changes the prefix string displayed by compute-sanitizer.
  --print-level arg (=warn)             <info|warn|error|fatal> Set the minimum level of errors to print.
  --print-limit arg (=10000)            When this is set, compute-sanitizer will stop printing errors after reaching the given number of errors.
                                        Use 0 for unlimited printing.
  --read arg                            Reads error records from a given file, previously generated with --save.
  --require-cuda-init arg (=yes)        Control if the tool should return an error code when the target application does not use CUDA
  --save arg                            Saves the error record to file.
                                        The sequence %p in the string name will be replaced by the pid of the compute-sanitizer application.
                                        The sequence %q{FOO} will be replaced by the value of the environment variable FOO. If the environment variable
                                        is not defined, it will be replaced by an empty string.
                                        The sequence %% is replaced by a literal % in the file name.
                                        Any other character following % will cause an error.
  --show-backtrace arg (=yes)           Display a backtrace on error.
                                        no     : No backtrace shown
                                        host   : Only host backtrace shown
                                        device : Only device backtrace shown for precise errors
                                        yes    : Host and device backtraces shown
                                        See the manual for more information
  --target-processes arg (=application-only)
                                        Select which processes are to be tracked by compute-sanitizer:
                                        application-only : Track only the root application process
                                        all              : Track the root application and all its child processes
  --tool arg (=memcheck)                Set the tool to use.
                                        memcheck  : Memory access checking
                                        racecheck : Shared memory hazard checking
                                        synccheck : Synchronization checking
                                        initcheck : Global memory initialization checking

Memcheck-specific options:
  --leak-check arg (=no)                <full|no> Print leak information for CUDA allocations.
                                        NOTE: Program must end with cudaDeviceReset() for this to work.
  --padding arg (=0)                    Size in bytes for padding buffer to add after each allocation.
  --report-api-errors arg (=explicit)   Print errors if any API call fails.
                                        all      : Report all CUDA API errors, including APIs invoked implicitly
                                        explicit : Report errors in explicit CUDA API calls only
                                        no       : Disable reporting of CUDA API errors

Racecheck-specific options:
  --racecheck-num-hazards arg (=32768)  Maximum number of racecheck hazards to record per-launch for a single SM.
  --racecheck-report arg (=analysis)    The reporting mode that applies to racecheck.
                                        all      : Report all hazards and race analysis reports.
                                        hazard   : Report only hazards.
                                        analysis : Report only race analysis reports.

Initcheck-specific options:
  --track-unused-memory arg (=no)       Check for unused memory allocations.

Please see the compute-sanitizer manual for more information.

